iamaileen.com 2019-05-22

# Disclaimer – iAmAileen.com

### TERMS OF USE

For “[https://iamaileen.com](https://iamaileen.com/ "I am Aileen")” / “[I am Aileen](https://iamaileen.com/ "I am Aileen")” | From 2014 to Present

This website is for general information purposes only and it is written, managed, and edited only by me (the author, Aileen A.).

The reading of all information on this website is of your own free will and if you do not accept the terms contained in this disclaimer, you should cease the use of this website immediately. (I reserve the right to change any of these terms at any given time.)

Firstly, all views that are expressed here represent only those made by myself and not those of any other person or entity in their favor. However, whatever opinion I may put across does not intend to harm, slander, or defame any company, individual, or thing. I will not be held liable for libel nor will I be held to compensate you in any way whatsoever if you ever happen to suffer a loss/inconvenience/damage because of what I may display or state in my blog. I will not even be responsible for what people might do with my advice, critique and/or wisdom.

I will definitely try my best to provide up-to-date information, but I can’t make representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Again: you are reading the information on this website on your own free will and you will be provided with information at your own risk.

Under no circumstances will I be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with the use of this website. Any reliance you place on any information gleaned from this blog is strictly at your own risk so please make sure to research and verify the information that you read from my blog because there’s a possibility that some of it will be less accurate as time passes.

### INTELLECTUAL & COPYRIGHT POLICY

All photos and text used in this site are intellectual properties of Aileen A. (me) unless otherwise stated. Additionally: unless otherwise noted, I am also the legal copyright holder of the material on this website and it may not be used, reprinted, (partially) modified, or published without my permission, especially if it’s for commercial use. If you would like to use any of the photos or text found in my website, please [get in touch with me](https://iamaileen.com/contact/ "Contact Page") first and do state your intent and purpose for such.

If you wish to repost or share any material from this website, please make sure to credit me by including my link(s). I absolutely don’t allow the reposting of my articles in its entirety so if you want to share an article, again: please include the link and if you really need some content, just take a small snippet from the article and NOT the whole of it.

(I do credit all the materials that are not from me—if and when I failed to properly credit you or any material, I sincerely apologize for that; such was not my intention. However, please do [let me know](https://iamaileen.com/contact "Contact Page") immediately about it so that I could take action for as soon as possible.)

### OTHER CONTENT MATTERS

I cannot be held responsible for any offense taken due to translation, interpretation or mistakes in grammar and/or punctuation of my website’s content. I will also not be liable if for any reason the website is unavailable at any time or at any period of time as I might often do so without notice and at my own discretion, intended or not.

Meanwhile, comments on this website are the sole responsibility of their writers and they will take full responsibility, liability, and blame for any libel or proceedings that will result from their statement. I do not even guarantee the accuracy, honesty and politeness of their comments. Though of course, I reserve the rights to edit or delete any comments submitted to this website without notice as they may deem to be spam or questionable spam, or that they include profanity, contain language or concepts that are offensive, attack a group or person individually, etc.

Should my website be unintentionally linked to obscene, pornographic, disgusting, hostile or offensive content-filled web pages, I, in no way condone, endorse or take responsibility for such. But indeed, this website contains links that direct to external websites and these are simply mainly provided for your convenience and information. Take note, however, that I am NOT in control of these platforms so I will not be held liable for any material contained within them.

### PRIVACY POLICY/STATEMENT

Any personal and/or contact information provided to me will be kept private (especially the emails from readers in blog comments and emails from newsletter subscribers). You will not be spammed in any way and I will absolutely not sell or disclose your information to any other companies.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

There are 3rd-party applications, however, like Google Analytics that would collect cookie and usage data. This basically means that Google will simply analyze visitor behavior in an **anonymous** form in order to track, examine and compile statistical reports on the traffic, activity and visits in this website.

Rest assured and overall, **NO** personal and identifiable information will be collected from you since your anonymity is still and always perfectly safe with iAmAileen.com

####  **MORE INFO ABOUT THIS SITE'S PRIVACY POLICY**

I am Aileen found at https://iamaileen.com/ (“Website”) is governed by the following privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”).

I respect your privacy and am committed to protecting it. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you what personally identifiable information this site may collect and how it may be used. This statement only applies to this Website.

**_What information do I collect and how is it used?_**

  * Information you voluntarily submit to the Website: I may collect personal information from you such as your name or email address. For example, you may voluntarily submit information to the Website by leaving a comment, subscribing to a newsletter, or submitting a contact form. In addition, you are able to create a user profile, which allows you to create a username and password. We will store the username, but your password will not be visible in our records.
  * Automatically-collected information: I automatically collect certain information about you and the device with which you access the Website. For example, when you use the Website, I will log your IP address, operating system type, browser type, referring website, pages you viewed, and the dates/times when you accessed the Website. I may also collect information about actions you take when using the Website, such as links clicked.
  * Cookies: I may log information using cookies, which are small data files stored on your browser by the Website. I may use both session cookies, which expire when you close your browser, and persistent cookies, which stay on your browser until deleted, to provide you with a more personalized experience on the Website.

**_How your information may be used_**  
I may use the information collected in the following ways:

  * To operate and maintain the Website;
  * To create your account, identify you as a user of the Website, and customize the Website for your account;
  * To send you promotional information, such as newsletters. Each email promotion will provide information on how to opt-out of future mailings;
  * To send you administrative communications, such as administrative emails, confirmation emails, technical notices, updates on policies, or security alerts;
  * To respond to your comments or inquiries;
  * To provide you with user support;
  * To track and measure advertising on the Website;
  * To protect, investigate, and deter against unauthorized or illegal activity.

**_Third-party use of personal information_**  
I may share your information with third parties when you explicitly authorize me to share your information.

Additionally, the Website may use third-party service providers to service various aspects of the Website. Each third-party service provider’s use of your personal information is dictated by their respective privacy policies.

The Website currently uses the following third-party service providers:

_Google Analytics_ – this service tracks Website usage and provides information such as referring websites and user actions on the Website. Google Analytics may capture your IP address, but no other personal information is captured by Google Analytics.

_Mail Chimp_ – this service is used for delivery of email updates and newsletters. We store your name and email address for purposes of delivering such communications. Please refer to Mail Chimp’s privacy policy for further information.

At this time, your personal information is not shared with any other third-party applications. This list may be amended from time to time in the Website’s sole discretion.

Except when required by law, I will not sell, distribute, or reveal your email addresses or other personal information without your consent; however, I may disclose or transfer personal information collected through the Website to third parties who acquire all or a portion of my business, which may be the result of a merger, consolidation, or purchase of all or a portion of our assets, or in connection with any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding brought by or against us.

**_Anonymous data_**  
From time to time, I may use anonymous data, which does not identify you alone, or when combined with data from other parties. This type of anonymous data may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Examples of this anonymous data may include analytics or information collected from cookies.

**_Publicly visible information_**  
If you create a user profile on the Website or leave a comment, certain information may be publicly visible. To create a user profile, you must choose a username and password and input your email address for profile confirmation. Your email address will never be available publicly. At your option, you may also add an avatar, a profile description, and a link to your website.

You may also choose to link your Facebook, Instagram, and Google Account. Users may see your username, avatar, profile description and website information.

**_Cookies_**  
The Website uses cookies to store visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, customize Website content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends. Cookies may also be used by third-party services, such as Google Analytics, as described herein.

Users may, at any time, prevent the setting of cookies, by the Website, by using a corresponding setting of your internet browser and may thus permanently deny the setting of cookies. Furthermore, already set cookies may be deleted at any time via an Internet browser or other software programs. This is possible in all popular Internet browsers. However, if users deactivate the setting of cookies in your Internet browser, not all functions of our Website may be entirely usable.

**_Advertising_**  
_Display Ads_  
I may use third-party advertising companies to serve content and advertisements when you visit the Website, which may use cookies, as noted above.

_Retargeting Ads_  
From time to time, the Website may engage in remarketing efforts with third-party companies, such as Google, Facebook, or Instagram, in order to market the Website. These companies use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Website.

_Affiliate Program Participation_  
The Website may engage in affiliate marketing, which is done by embedding tracking links into the Website. If you click on a link for an affiliate partnership, a cookie will be placed on your browser to track any sales for purposes of commissions. For example, I am Aileen is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and links to Amazon.com. As part of this Amazon Associates program, the Website will post customized links, provided by Amazon, to track the referrals to their website. This program utilizes cookies to track visits for the purposes of assigning commission on these sales.

_Newsletters_  
On the Website, you may subscribe to my newsletter, which may be used for advertising purposes. All newsletters sent may contain tracking pixels. The pixel is embedded in emails and allows an analysis of the success of online marketing campaigns. Because of these tracking pixels, I may see if and when you open an email and which links within the email you click. Also, this allows the Website to adapt the content of future newsletters to the interests of the user. This behavior will not be passed on to third parties.

**_Rights related to your personal information_**  
_Opt-out_ – You may opt-out of future email communications by following the unsubscribe links in my emails. You may also notify me at aileen@iamaileen.com to be removed from my mailing list.

_Access_ – You may access the personal information I have about you by submitting a request to aileen@iamaileen.com

_Amend_ – You may contact me at aileen@iamaileen.com to amend or update your personal information.

_Forget_ – In certain situations, you may request that I erase or forget your personal data. To do so, please submit a request to aileen@iamaileen.com.

Please note that I may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes or to complete transactions, or when required by law.

**_Sensitive personal information_**  
At no time should you submit sensitive personal information to the Website. This includes your social security number, information regarding race or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious beliefs, health information, criminal background, or trade union memberships. If you elect to submit such information to me, it will be subject to this Privacy Policy.

**_Children’s information_**  
The Website does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 16. If a parent or guardian believes that the Website has personally identifiable information of a child under the age of 16 in its database, please contact me immediately at aileen@iamaileen.com and I will use my best efforts to promptly remove such information from my records.

**_Contact information_**  
At any time, please contact me at aileen@iamaileen.com for questions related to this Privacy Policy. 

### ADVERTISERS & SPONSORS DISCLOSURE

This blog is also open to forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions, and other forms of compensation and/or projects. But even though this blog is open to advertising, I will never recommend and write about products or brands that I don’t personally use nor believe in. I will always disclose whether I will be receiving any commissions or products for free, or if a trip was sponsored or not.

But I am definitely not responsible for the actions of my advertisers or sponsors. If you purchase a product or service based upon a link from my website, you must take action with that company to resolve any issues and NOT with me. Any product, claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

What’s more is that some of the links on the website are affiliate or referral links. At no additional cost to you, I will earn a small percentage of the sale if you make a purchase through my affiliate link or I will earn a bonus from your registration through my referral link. In fact, the cost for you will sometimes even be cheaper due to my partnership with a certain brand — so it’s a “win-win” situation for the both of us. Rest assured, I only support things that I trust and have personally used. Ultimately, I hope for your understanding that this is a way for me to keep this website running in tiptop shape; so your purchases or registration through any of my affiliate links is much appreciated!

### CONTACT

Any letters, e-mails, blog comments, responses on Social Media platforms such as Facebook, Pinterest, Instagram, Youtube, and Twitter, or questions written directly to me may be used as blog material for my audience unless specifically requested otherwise. (Part of) these letters or emails, questions or any other feedback may be used in newsletters, blog posts, columns or up-and-coming books.

For any further clarifications and questions, it can all be directed to me at [](mailto:aileen@iamaileen.com)
